Guide to the Henry Burt Wright Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Addendum, Series V
  - Letters from Yale Graduates
    - Lines, Edwin Stevens (1845-1927) (Box 29)
    - Lyman, James (1862-1934) (Box 29)
    - McClure, James Gore King (1848-1932) (Box 29)
    - McKee, W C (Box 29)
    - Miller, George Douglas (1847-1932) (Box 29)
    - Morse, Richard Cary (1841-1926) (Box 29)
    - Northrop, Cyrus (1834-1922) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Noyes, Edward McArthur (1858-1939) (Box 29)
    - Payson, George Shipman (1845-1923) (Box 29)
    - Perry, David Brainerd (1839-1912) (Box 29)
    - Richards, Charles Edward (1859-1942) (Box 29)
    - Richards, William Rogers (1853-1910) (Box 29)
    - Salisbury, Edward Elbridge (1814-1901) (Box 29)
    - Savage, George Slocum Folger (1817-1915) (Box 29)
    - Schwab, John Christopher (1865-1916) (Box 29)
    - Scudder, Doremus (1858-1942) (Box 29)
    - Selden, Edward Griffin (1847-1904) (Box 29)
    - Sellers, James Cadwalader (1854-1928) (Box 29)
    - Smith, Moses (1830-1904) (Box 29)
    - Stone, George Frederick (1847-1927) (Box 29)
    - Strong, Charles Hall (1850-1914) (Box 29)
    - Sweet, Edwin Forrest (1847-1935) (Box 29)
    - Thacher, John Seymour (1856-1922) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Torrey, Reuben Archer (1856-1928) (Box 29)
    - Turner, Douglas Kellogg (1823-1902) (Box 29)
    - Vincent, Boyd (1845-1935) (Box 29)
    - Whitehead, John Meek (1852-1924) (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Collection of note cards and postcards
    - Collection of note cards and postcards related to Europe and European history, "made and used for Yale history courses". (Box 30)